watch the videos on the YouTube channel
go through the introductory like the
intro playlist that you've made you know
educate yourself the best you can so
that you are the best expert you can be
and not everybody can devour this stuff
but try just do something to get the
basics down and then you're going to
know real quick and even if you go to an
endocrinologist or an ex eurologist or
whatever that's fine to try and then
when they start going okay we're going
to put you on 100 milligrams every two
weeks and an aromatase and hi you go I'm
not doing that that's just what you say
you don't even go oh you don't bargain
with them you just go no we're not going
to be a right fit now unless you say I
want to do you know 60 milligrams twice
a week to start no AI Noone this and
they go okay that's fine well then maybe
you found somebody that's at least
reasonable but in general you're not g
to find reasonable people when it comes
to hormone replacement in the
traditional medical community it's
usually going to be people that have
probably already left that system or
never went that traditional route to
begin with not everybody I mean you're G
to find Diamonds in the Rough but again
that's all just random and lucky you you
there's no great database to search for
help me find an insurance-based provider
that knows what they're talking about
and doing with hormones there's no
there's no good way to search for that
so you may just get lucky but in general
you're G to be better off probably going
with a cash pay type place but even then
it it's a mindfield when it comes to
because a lot of the big box clinics
don't give a crap either and they're
just pushing product they don't and
they're pushing in Roman Inhibitors so
this is where again educate yourself so
that when you go and talk to these
places you know pretty quick whether
they actually have care about this topic
or not